realtycms.com 2013-11-25

# RealtyCMS

We Respect Your Privacy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At ZeniDev we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * Throughout our offerings, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

ZeniDev operates a network of websites including this one. It is ZeniDev's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, ZeniDev collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ZeniDev's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ZeniDev's visitors use its websites. From time to time, ZeniDev may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its websites. ZeniDev also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to ZeniDev's websites choose to interact with ZeniDev in ways that require ZeniDev to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ZeniDev gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with ZeniDev are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, ZeniDev collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with ZeniDev. ZeniDev does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

ZeniDev may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. ZeniDev may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ZeniDev does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ZeniDev discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ZeniDev's behalf or to provide services available at ZeniDev's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ZeniDev's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ZeniDev will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ZeniDev discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when ZeniDev believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ZeniDev, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an ZeniDev website and have supplied your email address, ZeniDev may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with ZeniDev and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs and Twitter to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ZeniDev takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ZeniDev uses cookies to help ZeniDev identify and track visitors, their usage of ZeniDev website, and their website access preferences. ZeniDev visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ZeniDev's websites, with the drawback that certain features of ZeniDev's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Business Transfers

If ZeniDev, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that ZeniDev goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of ZeniDev may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ZeniDev and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ZeniDev may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at ZeniDev's sole discretion. ZeniDev encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
